Tyme Bleyaert Full-Stack .NET developer

Last update: April 29, 2024

Residence

LinkedIn

LinkedIn

LinkedIn

Email

tyme.bleyaert@gmail.com

Up-to-date version of CV is available at

https://Tyme-Bleyaert.github.io/cv-enlgish-private

Full-stack .NET developer with over 2 years of experience. In the last years, I worked with: Winforms / WPF / Angular / Blazor / ASP.Net / DevExtreme for frontend, and for backend: Windows services / Entity Framework / ADO / RDO / SQL and Blazor server.

Professional Experience

December 2023 - April 2024

De Jaeger Automation Byba

Senior full-stack .NET developer



Developed a web based guidance application from scratch using Blazor and web API, ensuring scalability and performance.

Responsibilities:

- · Performing code reviews
- Mentoring junior developers
- · Promoting best coding practices
- · Maintaining build and release pipelines
- · Analyzing product performance issue
- Designing and developing new products
- Writing unit tests
- · Writing code based on SOLID principles
- · Creating project time-, budget- and scope analysis
- · Evaluate and select third-party tools and libraries for new projects
- Provide technical leadership and guidance for the team

July 2021 - November 2023

De Jaeger Automation Byba

Full-stack .NET developer

Working on the ProSuite framework, improving stability and performance. Creating and designing new features for the framework.

Responsibilities:

- · Promoting best coding practices
- Maintaining build and release pipelines
- Analyzing product performance issue
- Designing and developing new products
- Writing unit tests
- · Writing code based on SOLID principles

Reference(s):

Ronald Van Laerebeke (coo) +32 (0)9 379 50 52

Various temporary positions

Laborer

Education

.NET Developer C# - VDAB [18/11/2020 - 04/07/2021]
Basic IT - VDAB [18/08/2020 - 17/11/2020]
Game Development - Howest Kortrijk [2015 - 2016]
Web Development - Syntra West [2014 - 2015]
Accounting & Informatics - GO! Atheneum Maldegem [2014]

Skills



Additional Experience

Passionate about working on my .NET library and providing assistance to other developers on open source projects (GitHub).

